DANIEL KEBEDE

Software Engineer

CONTACT

- +251921154404
- ✓ danielkebede38@gmail.com
- Addis ababa , Ayat
- https://github.com/danielkeb

PROFILE SUMMARY

I'm passionate and hardworking software engineer with experience in building web and mobile application development. As an experienced developer, i excel in all stages of advanced web development and am skilled in both self managing independent projects and collaborating effectively in team settings

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 DEBRE BIRHAN UNIVERSITY

- Bachelor degree of software Eng.
- GPA: 3.58 / 4.0
- Exit Exam: 69/100

SKILLS

- Web development
- Mobile App devellopment
- Git
- Postgresql/mysql
- Technology(laravel, Django, Express>js, NestJs, angular, Nextjs, React and Flutter)
- Programming language(c++, java, php, python, javascript, typescript, Dart)

0

WORK EXPERIENCE

Abune gorgoriwos School Management system

January 2024- May 2024

FullStack web and mobile application developer

- Implemented REST API integration to dynamically retrieve and synchronize data between the server, web application, and mobile application, with role-based API protection.
- Designed an attractive and user-friendly interface to enhance the end-user experience.
- Successfully developed a comprehensive school management system to meet all the client's requirements.

Debre Birhan univesity PRMs project

May 2024- August 2024

FullStack web and Mobile App developer

- I implemented and developed a nestjs Api that requires PRMS(personal computer registration management system) and a barcode generator Api, with role based api protection for enhanced security.
- I also developed an easy to use interface for web application and a mobile application that includes a barcode scanner, ensuring a seamless and intuitive user experience across platform.

LANGUAGES

• English: Conversation

• Amharic: Fluent

Oromic: conversation



ደብረ ብርሃን ዩኒቨርሲቲ

DEBRE BERHAN UNIVERSITY

የፊጅስትራር ጽ/ቤት

Office of the Registrar



ለሚመለከተው ሁሉ

ደንኤል ከበደ ካሳ በመደብኛው መርሃግብር ከ ከምፒቲንን ሳ୫ንስ ኮሌጅ የጊዜንስ ባችለር ዲግሪ በሶፍትዌር ምሀንደስና የትምሀርት መስክ በ 26/10/2016 ዓ.ም.

ውጤቱም በአጠቃላይ <u>3.58</u> *ሲሆን ሰኔ 2016 ዓ.ም የተሰጠውን አ<i>ገር አቀፍ የመውጫ ፈተና 69% በጣምጣት ያለፈ መሆኑን እየገለጽን ፤* ዋናው ዲግሪና ትራንስከሪፕት በውጭ መጋራት ውል መሰረት ግጲታውን ሲወጣ የሚሰጥ



To Whom It May Concern

This Certificate is issued to <u>DANIEL KEBEDE</u>
<u>KASA</u> upon his graduation from <u>College of</u>
<u>Computing Sciences</u> in the regular program with <u>Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering</u> on <u>July 03, 2024</u> with <u>CGPA</u> of <u>3.58</u>. He took the National Exit Examination in <u>June 2024</u> and passed with a score of 69%.

The Original Diploma and Transcript will be issued upon the discharge of cost sharing duty.

68076-C/Registral Trail of Letter Human (Phil)

Tel:+251-116813418

P.O.BOX:445
DEBRE BERHAN, Ethiopia